This is Nitrna, I am Aika Kine from C4.
This is the third game project.
Please give me your best regards.
What is the game you are going to challenge this time?
What is it?
It's "Don't laugh, read aloud".
What's that?
I will explain the rules of the "Don't Laugh Aloud" game.
You will take turns reading aloud a story from the textbook.
However, you must read aloud according to the various instruction cards.
You may change the words or add movements.
If either the reader or listener laughs, a chalk tip will be taken.
The person who has the most chalk chips when the story is read aloud will be the winner.
I didn't understand it at first, but now I might understand it a little better.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
I'm a little worried that I'm going to make you laugh a lot.
Really?
Because you haven't even looked at the subject matter.
That's right.
I wonder what they'll come up with.
I don't know if I can handle it.
I laugh at things I'm not supposed to laugh at.
I wonder if I'll be okay... since I've been told absolutely not to laugh.
I'll do my best not to laugh.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors first.
I guess it doesn't have to be like this anymore.
Okay, today we'll read "Red Riding Hood." Let's begin.
Let's start with the music "Don't Laugh, Don't Laugh, Don't Laugh
Chapter 1: Little Red Riding Hood
Once upon a time, there was a little girl... and everyone loved her, but her grandmother...
Everyone loved the little girl, but her grandmother loved her most of all.
Once upon a time, Grandmother dressed this very pretty little girl in a lovely red velvet zukin.
One day, the Grandmother gave her a cute red velvet zukin.
It looked so good on her that everyone started calling her Red Zukin.
What?
One day.
Redskin's mudders,
Red?
Here's a bottle of grape wine, a snack.
Take this to your grandmother.
Where was I going with this?
Your grandmother is sick and weak.
But if you take a sip of this, she'll get better.
On the way to your grandmother's
Don't get sidetracked on the way to your grandmother's.
And don't forget to say hello when you enter her room.
Good, good, good.
What a compliment.
He gave me a compliment.
You're good.
What?
You just laughed twice.
I'll go.
It's okay. I'll go.
Little Red Riding Hood said so,
And she and her mother cut each other's fingers.
Grandmother's house,
It took half an hour's walk from the village to get there.
Little Red Riding Hood goes into the woods...
When she stopped going into the forest, the wolf came out at a higher elevation,
A wolf came out to the top of the hill.The wolf came out on the elevation.
The Little Red Riding Hood,
Go ahead and ignore me now.
Okay, I'll start with me.
I didn't know what it was at first.
At first,
It was flirtatious.
It wasn't flirtatious at all.
He was serious.
That's for sure.
You don't have any dialogue yet.
That's true.
That's for sure. It was difficult at first.
I finally did it in a flirtatious way.
Just in case. I did it just for the sake of it.
But I was faithful.
The next one was amazing.
It was amazing.
Then, the first question.
After that. I was,
English in places.
I see. So you are speaking English in places.
It wasn't good.
It was like someone from overseas
I thought it was a subject for foreign people who just started to learn Japanese.
I thought it was a subject like foreigners just started to learn Japanese.
But when you think of English at a time like this
I really can't come up with anything.
Japanese people.
I said "sake" one time.
Sake is an English word, isn't it?
I said alcohol.
Alcohol?
And then I took one away.
That was funny.
Okay, I'll do the next one like a rap song.
Yeah, that's right. You were so good.
It was so good, I laughed.
I thought it was really good, and I recognized it right away.
I took it.
So far, I won.
And at the end.
At the end, I was still good.
I see. I thought it would be sexy.
I thought I was going to hear the first line out of the blue.
I was pretty excited.
I'm just not ready for it yet.
I'm still not good at it yet.
It's very sexy.
Really?
Rin PDesz någonting or tell you
My subject will go first.
The Great Emperor.
Hello, little Red Riding Hood.
Little Red Riding Hood.
So early.
Said the wolf.
Hello
Mr. Wolf.
We're going to your grandmother's.
We're going.Go on.
What's that you're holding under your apron?
What is it?
It's scary.
Sweets and wine
Your grandmother is weak.
But these will give her strength.
Where does your grandmother live?
In the deepest part of the forest
Under a big oak tree.
Who's there? I'm scared.
Let's go that way.
Okay, okay.
Now.
The wolf speaks softly, but he's really a bad wolf.
A young, tender little thing.
This one's got a nice fat taste.
Well, get creative. Treat them both.
The wolf walked with Little Red Riding Hood for a while and then said...
Little Red Riding Hood, look at all the pretty flowers blooming there.
And Little Red Riding Hood opened her eyes.
There are so many beautiful flowers all around.
Bouquet for Granny
If I made a bouquet for Granny, I'm sure she'd be very pleased.
Akarukin-chan went off to the side to pick up the flowers.
But the wolf, in the meantime, went to her grandmother's house.
When he arrived at the house under the big oak tree, he opened the door with a bang.
Who is it? said the grandmother.
The wolf pretended to be Akazuki, and said
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Let's play.
I've brought sweets and wine. Open the door.
Oh, it's you. Come in.
The wolf opened the door, and he went right into Granny's bedroom.
He swallowed her up in one gulp.
Then he put on her kimono and her hood and lay down on her bed.
Then he put on his grandmother's kimono, put on his grandmother's hood, lay down on her bed, and drew the curtains around her bed.
What do you think?
What's the end?
At first I was like the Witch Queen. The Witch Queen, she scared me.
Scary? Yes, I was faithful. Yes!
I'm so happy! I was so surprised when you suddenly started speaking so loudly, and I couldn't even read you.
I thought, "Pull yourself together.
I'm glad to hear it! You're so loud all of a sudden, and I can't even read you.
Okay, I'll go next.
Like a newscaster... Very good, very good.
Really? I don't remember newscasters being like this. Yeah, but it was so easy to understand, and you were talking so sparkly, and...
I'm just saying, you know, it's a compliment.
I'm a little weepy. Good, good, good, good.
What was the last one? I'm like a TV shopping spree.
Like a TV shopping spree? Is there anything else?
I did my best, but I'm like that guy you see all the time.
The one beside you?
Yes, from the outside. - Wow!
I see... I see... That side...
Don't take that side so seriously.
I've been thinking about it since Madam just left.
Madame's so happy, she's going to get out!
So... we read aloud "Don't Laugh." Thank you very much. How was it?So, I read aloud "Don't Laugh." Thank you very much. How was it?
I'm fine now that I'm a madam. You wanted to do it? You wanted to do it?
That's funny!
Maomo won the lumplings. Thank you very much.
Well, I'll go with Maomo of Fukui from now on.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
Wow, that's close! What?
That was close!
Well, give me a lift home.
Sure. Thank you very much.
We did it! We won!
So, my opponents so far,
Idolna and Aiko Kinui-Nui from Sceneo!
Bye bye!